[SHELDON SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
No, it's:
[SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
(Howard:)What's this?
(Sheldon:)That's what you did.
(Sheldon:)I assumed, as in a number of languages,
that the gesture was part of the phrase.
- Well, it's not.
- Why am I supposed to know that?
As teacher, it's your obligation
to separate your personal idiosyncrasies...
(Sheldon:)...from the subject matter.
- I'm glad you decided to learn Mandarin.
- Why?
(Howard:)Once you're fluent, you'll have a
billion more people to annoy instead of me.
(Leonard(entering):)Hey.
[SPEAKING IN MANDARIN]
(Howard:)You just called Leonard
a syphilitic donkey.
(Sheldon:)My apologies, Leonard.
I'm only as good as my teacher.
(Leonard:)Why are you learning Chinese?
(Sheldon:)I believe the Szechuan Palace
has been passing off orange chicken...
(Sheldon:)...as tangerine chicken,
and I intend to confront them.
(Leonard:)If I were you, I'd be more concerned
about what they're passing off as chicken.
- I need to use your window.
- Oh, hey. Yeah, no, sure, go ahead.
Hey, jerk face. You forgot your iPod.
- What's going on?
- I'll tell you what's going on.
That stupid, self-centered bastard
wrote about our sex life in his blog.
(Penny:)Drop dead,
you stupid, self-centered bastard.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Okay, where were we?
(Howard:)Not now. I have a blog to find.